my_q_a = {
        '0': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question':'Which of the following methods will add one or more elements to the begenning of an array',
            'description': 'Choose from the options provided.',
            'choices': ['push()', 'shift()', 'unshift()', 'pop()'],
            'answer': ['unshift()']
        },
        '1': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'What dose the following print in console: console.log([1,2,3].pop())',
            'description': 'Choose from the options provided.',
            'choices': ['1,2', '3'],
            'answer': ['3']
        },
        '2': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Which method returns a shallow copy of a portion of an array into a new array.',
            'description': 'Choose from the options provided.',
            'choices': ['Slice', 'Splice'],
            'answer': ['Slice']
        },
        '3': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question':'Which of the following statements is correct',
            'description': 'Choose from the options provided.',
            'choices': ['A set can only contain 3 elements', 'A set can only contain 3 unique elements', 'All elements in a set are unique'],
            'answer': ['All elements in a set are unique']
        },
        '4': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'The _____  method calls a function with a given this value and arguments provided individually',
            'description': 'Choose the method to use.',
            'choices': ['call()', 'apply()'],
            'answer': ['call()']
        },
        '5': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Whcih of the following would give an array containing the number 7.',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['Arry(7)', 'Arry.of(7)', 'Arry(7,5)'],
            'answer': ['Arry.of(7)', 'Arry(7,5)']
        },
        '6': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question':'Name the four data types used in Python',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['Dictionary', 'List', 'Set', 'Tuple']
        },
        '7': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Which of the following, if any are valid',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['let add = x,y => x+y;', 'let addTo = x => x+5;', 'let addTo = (x) => {return x+5;}', 'let addTo = (x) => { x+5;}'],
            'answer': ['let addTo = x => x+5;', 'let addTo = (x) => {return x+5;}']
        },
        '8': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Is the following Valid  let add = (x = 5, y) => x+y;.',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['Invalid as no return statement','Valid as its an arrow function','Invalid: Optional parameters are defined at the end of the parameter list', 'Invalid as no {} used'],
            'answer': ['Invalid: Optional parameters are defined at the end of the parameter list']
        },
        '9': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question':'For fun what would the following show in console: let num=["10","20"]; +"10"+ ++num[0];',
            'description': 'Choose from the options provided.',
            'choices':['undefined','error message', '"1020"', 21, 20],
            'answer': ["21"]
        },
        '10': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question': 'Which of the following is a data type used in Python',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['array', 'tuple', 'set', 'object', 'dictionary'],
            'answer': ['dictionary', 'tuple', 'set']
        },
        '11': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Which of the following are javascript string methods.',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['reverse', 'replace', 'split', 'splice', 'slice'],
            'answer': ['replace', 'split']
        },
}
